Please subscribe to our channel and
follow us on Twitter.
Good morning.
You are in a familiar place.
But you are sad because you are in a
familiar place.
I don't want to be here.
Will this place disappear?
I think I have been too strict.
I agree.
I will tell you the truth.
I was consulted by HMV that there are
too many posters of Ibinari and HOKU.
Excited
I'm going to go to the poster.
I see.
You can find a place to post it.
I'm going to go crazy.
You can get permission to shoot and
post it.
I'm going to go crazy.
It's a sudden attack.
It's like a sudden attack.
I'm hungry.
I'm going to work now.
I'm going to eat at the place I'm going
to post it.
Can I give you a poster?
Yes, you can.
I'll give you a poster.
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
This is a little dangerous.
What is this?
I've done this before.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to make you sleep.
I'm not in trouble at all.
This is the live information of 2020.
I thought it was important that the
members came to post it.
I'm thinking about it if I can't give
it to you.
I'll tell you later.
I'm scared.
It's a mental problem.
I'm not mentally strong.
I'm sorry.
We're going to start.
I'm scared.
Let's do our best.
Taxi?
Taxi.
Let's go.
I'm going.
I'm scared.
The first place is E-BEANS.
I'm here at ROOF TOP V-GONDAE.
Congratulations.
I'm here at the place where Miu and
Kanae made.
We have collaborated for many years.
I'm going to do mental care here.
Who will you go to?
I'll go to Miu.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to put a poster.
Can you put a poster?
I'm done.
Are you OK?
Thank you.
I'm glad.
I'm sorry.
What did you try to write?
I got a new feeling.
What is this?
Is it a potato?
It's a potato.
It's a mother's day.
What is this?
There are many other delicious foods.
Please come here.
I put a poster.
I'm glad.
I'll go to all E-BEANS.
I'll go to the next store.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I'm
doing YouTube with a
sudden talk, but
I'm sure it's okay to put a poster.
Osu
Everyone, it started from the room all
of a sudden, so
I'm sure I'll tell you where it is.
This is Makana Sendai.
Yes, I'm going to the live house.
We are also
doing a special meeting here.
I did it.
I got permission, so I'm going to put
it on.
Yes.
I'm going to put something on my bangs.
That's right.
Is it English?
Then it will be Makana-chan.
By the way, is there anything you can't
recommend at the Jetsunagi?
I'm going to the
recommended place, but
there is a restaurant.
Restaurant?
McDonald's is at the top of this.
It's a big company.
Thank you very much.
Later.
Later?
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
I came to a shop called Yukimura.
I'll ask them how to get the poster.
Can you bring this poster to the shop?
Of course.
This is good, isn't it?
Thank you.
Please sign your autograph.
I'll do it.
I'm rooting for you.
I'm watching you.
Thank you.
Please do your best.
Please support us.
Thank you.
This looks delicious.
This is fried sweet potato.
Is it?
This is for you.
She wants to have lunch with us.
This is a Japanese beef steak.
It's written here.
This is a high-value beef tongue.
This is 700 yen.
It's cheap.
It's with coffee.
Is it?
It's cheap.
I want to eat it.
We've done it.
Please come to Yukimura's shop.
Please come to eat.
It's a Japanese beef steak set meal.
They have a lunch with a meal.
Please come to see the poster.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I'm going to put up a poster at a curry
shop called Reigen Bougen.
I'm going to draw a picture and put it
up.
Good.
I'm going to put up a poster at a curry
shop called Reigen Bougen.
Is it a salaryman?
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
уже 죽 Pierrot
Let's explore Nara more!
We are at the hotel.
We are going to the hotel.
I'm going to the hotel.
I'm a hostess.
Can I put up a poster?
Yes, you can.
Thank you.
This is a curse.
I can feel energetic when I put this
on.
I'm afraid I'll be caught.
Have you ever drunk?
Yes, I have.
Really?
Yes.
I like small ones.
Really?
Do you want to drink?
I'll make you something to drink.
What?
Thank you.
Let's eat.
Congratulations.
I'll measure it.
Please measure it.
It looks delicious.
It's not a back-up plan.
I want to do it.
It's the opposite of the natural.
We are 9 people.
I thought you had quit.
It's too hard.
It's not like that.
You are here.
Yes, I am.
Then, you should come as 9 people.
Yes, I will.
Thank you.
Good luck.
It's so hot.
It's hot.
It's hot when it's cold.
Excuse me.
I'm from Tohoku.
I'm a tour guide.
Thank you.
I'm shooting for YouTube.
Is it okay to shoot here?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm shooting for YouTube for a day.
I'm going to various stores without an
appointment.
I'm going to put up this poster.
I want to put up this poster for you,
too.
I'm happy.
Is it okay?
Yes.
Okay.
Thank you.
Please put this poster.
Okay. Thank you.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to cry.
I'm so excited.
I don't care if I'm a coward
Sweetheart
All right!
I have fallen for a pretty and lucid
lady
Let's have a good time together
I'm a Garrot scoupe and I'm the south
sea
I'm cured of the blemishes
I'll wear a beanie and cover my heart
I'll open the door to the entrance
The outcome of the game is B, after all
I wonder if I should go with that
If I still get lost and raise my head
I'll take a deep breath
My, my, my, my, my, my partner is BN
Even if I get lost, I won't be afraid
I'll go anywhere, I don't care
I'm a free girl
You're a good girl, but you're a good
girl when you're not
I'm sad, I'm awake, it was all a dream
The sun is bright again today, I have
to go to school
Even if I laugh
That's fine
I'm not afraid of anything
No problem
I don't care if I'm a knight
Sweetheart
All night
No matter how long it takes
I'll be by your side
Please subscribe to our channel!
I'm so happy right now, I'm so happy
right now
You're such a cute girl
But you're not
I'm so happy right now, I'm so happy
right now
I'm happy.
Let's put up a poster and go home.
I haven't done it yet.
I haven't put up a poster yet.
The poster is ready.
Yeah!
Ready, set, go!
OK!
Thank you!
So, let's go back to HMV and report to
the manager.
Let's go!
Thank you!
Thank you for your hard work!
It was a good day!
Good job!
Vegetable chain!
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to my channel!
I'm back at HMV.
We walked a lot.
It's been a while since we walked.
We walked in the rain.
Good job, everyone.
Good job.
We have a poster.
We came back to report to the manager.
This is the second time to visit the
hair salon.
Thank you.
We got a lot of posters.
This is the number of posters we have.
Thank you.
Do you want to decorate your house?
I don't mind.
Do you want to decorate all of them?
Where do you want to put them?
We can decorate the passage.
Is it okay?
We couldn't give them all to you.
So, we will sign all of them and give
them to you.
Really?
I'm worried about HMV.
Let's move to the next place.
Yes.
We did it.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Yuna is impossible.
She is like a mature person.
She is always like this.
She is in my heart.
Yuna is impossible.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I often see a comment like this.
If a tennis player wins, I will write
here.
Viewer's gift.
I want to play.
I want to do something secret.
Secret?
What is it?
I'm going to be a beauty.
We put posters on all the walls of HMV.
Thank you so much.
I've never had such an experience.
We put our autographs and comments on
all the walls.
When you come to HMV, please check this
place.
We got to know many new shops.
I was surprised to hear that many
people knew this shop.
I was happy to hear that.
We got to know many new shops.
It's important.
I'll walk a lot to avoid being called
Halloween.
I look like Halloween when I walk.
Please look forward to next week.
Bye bye.
Please give us a high rating.
Please visit this shop.